<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<ModMetaData>
	<name>The Witcher Trials v2.0</name>
	<author>Imoja</author>
	<url></url>
	<targetVersion>0.19.2009</targetVersion>
	<description>
Above image created by 'alexnegrea' of DeviantArt.
(Please save your game FIRST. These operations unbalance vanilla pawns, and failed operations may kill your pawns.)

[h1]Introduction[/h1]	
This mod allows you to research the ancient Witcher trials and perform the procedures on your pawns. You are able to research:[list]
[*] The Trial of the Grasses: The first trial. The body is manipulated with herbs, toxins and poisons. This primarily affects the nervous system.
[*] The Trial of the Dreams: The second trial. The mutation of the eyes, hormones and bone marrow is performed. This also results in infertility.
[*] The Trial of the Elders: The final trial. Forgotton practices were once performed on the legendary White Wolf. You too can uncover these secrets, and pay the price.
[/list]

[h1]What it actually does[/h1]	
There are three operations, The trials of: Grasses, Dreams and Elders. You can think of these as stage 1, 2 and 3.
Each operation will overwrite the previous Trial.
All stages only have a 3 in 10 chance of success. However, early stages have a lower chance of death on failure.
The trials can be researched immediately, but it takes a very long time research. Each trial only requires Medicinal Herbs.

As the stages progress, a pawn becomes far more powerful, and easier to manage. The downside is that they lose social skills. The changes this mod makes are not listed here as to be a bit of a suprise, this will likely change.

[h1]What i'd like to implement[/h1][list]
[*] Procedures must be performed in order, and are not reversible.
[/list]

[h1]FAQ:[/h1][list]
[*]When I apply a new Trial, the old one disappears? - This is expected behaviour. Its easier to calculate the balance of the mod when only one Trial is being applied to the stats. This is subject to change.
[/list]

[h1]CHANGELOG:[/h1][list]
[*]v1.0 - Initial release
[*]v1.1 - Modified comfortable temperature range. (+0/-5, +5/-10, +10/-15)
[*]v1.2 - Stage 3 changes pawn hair colour to white.
[/list]

Feedback encouraged.
	</description>
</ModMetaData>
